# KAMIL MAZELANIK

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a front-end developer with 2 years of experience in designing and building responsive web design. Specialises in React.js, responsive design, HTML, CSS and JavaScript. On a daily basis I use: version control system - GIT and Jira software. I find myself well in a team.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Front-end Developer

Ework Group | 2021 - present

The application we are developing helps clients hire new employees and maintains their history, e.g. creating job request and work orders.

My tasks: developing and expanding application features. Creating reusable components according to design system. Bug fixing. Working in a scrum team. Contacting and collaborating with project managers, back-end/front-end developers and designers. Providing responsive views. Working with the GitLab platform.

Used tools: TypeScript, React.js library, React Query, React Router, Chart.js, Zod, Yup, Storybook, GitLab.

#### Non - IT related works

Constructor/Designer | 2013 - 2021

Working in CAD programs mainly for automotive.

# **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

#### Silesian University of Technology in Gliwice

Management and Production Engineering

Engineering degree - 09.2014 - 03.2018 Specialty - Production Systems Management

I hereby consent for my personal data to be processed for the purpose of conducting recruitment for the position for which I am applying.



# **CONTACT ME AT**



500-036-580



kamilmaz9206@gmail.com



Rybnik



http://www.linkedin.com/in/ kamil-mazelanik



https://github.com/Kaweight

# SKILLS SUMMARY

- TypeScript
- React.js
- Webpack
- Sass
- HTML
- Bootstrap
- Git
- Jira

#### LANGUAGES

- English: communicative (B2)
- Polish: native